{
    "subject": "resource/Will_Patton",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:American_male_actors",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Will Patton's work is American male actors.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8477534651756287,
            "question": "Why do you think Will Patton chose to focus on American male actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8253757953643799,
            "question": "What is the subject of Will Patton's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7352039813995361,
            "question": "What nationality are the actors Will Patton studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7182238698005676,
            "question": "What type of actors are featured in Will Patton's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6851528286933899,
            "question": "What are some examples of actors that might be included in Will Patton's work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6245840787887573,
            "question": "Is Will Patton's work about female actors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6060092449188232,
            "question": "Does Will Patton's work cover actors from different countries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.532146155834198,
            "question": "Who does Will Patton's work focus on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5075997114181519,
            "question": "What kind of profession does Will Patton likely have?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37074941396713257,
            "question": "Are there any specific time periods or eras focused on in Will Patton's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Will Patton's work is American male actors.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5567_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of profession does Will Patton likely have?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5567_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who does Will Patton's work focus on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5567_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Will Patton's work cover actors from different countries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5567_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_164.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_176.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5567_67.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Will Patton being an American actor, which supports the statement that the subject of his work involves American male actors."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "The provided text focuses on Will Patton's career as an actor, highlighting his roles in films and television series. There's no mention of him exclusively working with or focusing on American male actors.",
            "category": 4
        }
    }
}